>> Are you ready, kids?
>> 孩子们，准备好了吗？
All: Aye, aye, Captain!
全体：是啊是啊，队长！
>> I can't hear you.
>> 我听不到你说话。
All: Aye, aye, Captain!
全体：是啊是啊，队长！
>> ♪ Ohh... ♪
>> ♪ 哦... ♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
>> ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
>> ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
>> ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
>> Ready?
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> 准备好了吗？
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
海绵宝宝！
>> SpongeBob
>> 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
♪ ♪
>> Okay, Karen,
which one's better?
>> 好的，凯伦，
哪个更好？
>> If I had eyes,
I'd be rolling them right now.
>> 如果我有眼睛
我现在就会滚动它们。
>> Thanks for the help.
>> 感谢您的帮助。
You know,
details like this
你知道，
细节是这样的
can be very important
to the customers.
可能非常重要
给客户。
>> Customers?
>> 客户？
What customers?
什么客户？
>> Well, uh...
>> 嗯，呃...
Like those customers
who just pulled up.
就像那些顾客一样
谁刚刚停下来。
Hello, gentlemen,
and welcome to the Chum Bucket.
你好，先生们，
欢迎来到密友桶。
Would you like seating
inside or outside?
您想要座位吗
里面还是外面？
>> Seating for what?
>> 座位有什么用？
>> For the Chum Bucket!
>> 为了密友桶！
Where you can enjoy
a nice helping of chum.
在那里你可以享受
朋友的一个很好的帮助。
Oh, boy, this is so--
num, num, mm-hmm.
哦，孩子，这是这样的——
数字，数字，毫米-嗯。
Mmm, good,
the chum is.
嗯，好，
密友是。
>> Wait a minute.
Eating chum?
>> 等一下。
吃密友吗？
Do people do that?
人们这样做吗？
>> Look,
are you gonna eat or not?
>> 看，
你到底吃还是不吃？
>> Yeah, I'm gonna have
two Krabby Patties.
>> 是的，我要去
两个蟹肉饼。
>> Oh, yeah, two.
>> 哦，是的，两个。
>> We couldn't find parking
over there at the Krusty Krab.
>> 我们找不到停车位
就在蟹堡王那里。
Boom!
繁荣！
>>
>>
Ah!
啊!
Now, what was I saying?
现在，我刚才说什么？
Oh, right...
哦，对了...
I'm tired of the Krusty Krab
taking all of my business.
我厌倦了蟹堡王
抢走了我所有的生意。
We're doomed, Karen.
我们注定要失败，凯伦。
Doomed, I tell you.
注定了，我告诉你。
>> Well, why don't you do what
all good business owners do?
>> 那么，你为什么不做点什么呢？
都是优秀的企业主吗？
>> What would that be?
>> 那会是什么？
>> Advertise your product,
of course.
>> 为您的产品做广告，
当然。
>> Advertising?
>> 广告？
I can't believe it took me
this long to come up with this.
我不敢相信它花了我
这么长时间才想出这个。
>>
>>
>> Let's see...
"Q," no.
>> 让我们看看...
“问，”不。
"P," no.
Ah, here it is, "L."
“P”不。
啊，这里是“L”。
There, it's perfect.
在那里，它是完美的。
"Chum is metabolic fuel!"
“密友是新陈代谢的燃料！”
You really did it this time,
old Planky.
这次你真的做到了
老普朗基。
Oh, yeah.
Who's a genius?
哦，是的。
谁是天才？
♪ Have you seen this,
seen this, seen this ♪
♪ 你见过这个吗
看过这个看过这个♪
♪ Seen my genius,
genius, genius ♪
♪ 看到了我的天才，
天才啊天才♪
>> Chum is...
>> 密友是...
Meh...
嗯……
>> Hello, sir,
and welcome to the Chum Bucket.
>> 先生您好，
欢迎来到密友桶。
Uh, sir?
呃，先生？
>> Met-ah--uh...
ta-tub--uh...
>> 遇见啊--呃...
塔-图布——呃...
bol--ick!
太棒了！
>> Forget about
what that word means!
>> 忘记
这个词是什么意思！
There's a fire breaking out
in the language lobes.
发生火灾了
在语言叶中。
We need to get out of here!
我们需要离开这里！
>> The door is jammed!
>> 门被卡住了！
>> Push harder!
>> 更加努力！
>> Mm--meta-bu.
Bu-bu-boo.
>> 嗯--元-bu。
布布布。
>> Uh, sir?
Your head, it's on fire.
>> 呃，先生？
你的头，着火了。
The drink!
Use the drink!
饮料！
使用饮料！
>> It's kelp juice.
You want some?
>> 这是海带汁。
你想要一些吗？
Hey!
嘿！
What kind of friend are you?
你是什​​么样的朋友？
>> Friend?
I don't even know you.
>> 朋友？
我什至不认识你。
>> Go ahead.
Say you're sorry.
>> 继续吧。
说声对不起。
>> Uh, I'm sorry.
>> 呃，对不起。
>> Okay, I forgive you,
>> 好吧，我原谅你了，
and I'm sorry for yelling.
我很抱歉大喊大叫。
Okay, so can I tell you
something honestly?
好的，我可以告诉你吗
老实说？
>> Whatever.
>> 无论如何。
>> It's about your sign.
>> 这是关于你的标志。
These words
make my head sad.
这些话
让我头疼。
I don't get it.
我不明白。
It's okay, little fella.
没关系，小家伙。
I don't either.
我也不。
>> Okay, freak show.
You just wait.
>> 好吧，怪胎表演。
你等着吧。
In a few minutes,
几分钟后，
this sign will have attracted
more customers
这个标志将会吸引
更多客户
than you can count.
比你能数的还要多。
>> A few minutes later...
>> 几分钟后...
>> Uh, what's that number
before one?
>> 呃，那个数字是多少
在一个之前？
>> Zero.
>> 零。
>> Oh, right, congratulations!
>>哦，对了，恭喜你！
You have zero customers.
您的客户为零。
>> Okay, so maybe
it'll take a little longer
>> 好吧，也许
需要更长的时间
than a few minutes.
比几分钟。
>> A little longer
than a few minutes later...
>> 再长一点
几分钟后...
>> Wait.
What are we doing again?
>> 等等。
我们又在做什么？
Smack!
>>
咂！
>>
>> There we go.
>> 我们开始吧。
"Chum is fum!"
“嗯嗯！”
>> What the...
>> 这是什么...
This says,
"chum is fum."
这说，
“密友很生气。”
You changed my sign
to "chum is fum"?
你改变了我的标志
到“密友很开心”？
That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
这是最愚蠢的事
我曾经听说过。
>> They seem to think
it's interesting.
>> 他们似乎认为
这很有趣。
>> Apparently,
dumb sells chum.
>> 显然，
笨蛋卖密友。
And I believe I just found
our advertising director.
我相信我刚刚发现
我们的广告总监。
>> Only two customers?
>> 只有两个顾客？
Customers are looking
kind of scarce.
客户正在寻找
有点稀缺。
Must be low tide or something,
Eh, Squidward?
一定是退潮什么的
呃，章鱼哥？
>> They've all gone
to the Chum Bucket.
>> 他们都走了
到密友桶。
>> The Chum Bucket?
>> 密友桶？
Chum is fum?
密友是fum？
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
>> Yes, sir.
>>
>> 是的，先生。
>>
SpongeBob,
we have a situation.
海绵宝宝，
我们有一个情况。
>> I'm on it.
>> 我正在做。
Buzz!
嗡嗡声！
Five.
五。
Four.
四。
Three.
三。
Two.
二。
One.
一。
>> SpongeBob, I'm afraid our
worst fears have been realized.
>> 海绵宝宝，恐怕我们的
最糟糕的担心已经成为现实。
>>
Goofy Goober is going nondairy?
>>
高飞古伯（Goofy Goober）要转向非乳制品了吗？
>> No.
>> 没有。
>> Oh-hoo, slide show.
>> 噢，幻灯片放映。
>> A few hours ago,
>> 几个小时前，
the Chum Bucket was,
as it should be,
密友桶是，
理应如此，
a desolate no-man's-land.
荒凉的无人区。
There's only one way
只有一种方法
he could have turned things
around so quickly.
他本可以扭转局面
绕得这么快。
Plankton must have slipped
into the Krusty Krab
浮游生物肯定已经滑落了
进入蟹堡王
while you weren't looking.
当你不看的时候。
>> Hey, that's my legs!
>> 嘿，那是我的腿！
>> He stole the formula!
>> 他偷了配方！
>>
>>
>> I thought you'd say that.
>> 我以为你会这么说。
So we need to infiltrate
the Chum Bucket
所以我们需要渗透
密友桶
and steal the formula back.
并把公式偷回来。
>> Ah!
>> 啊！
>> SpongeBob,
how you holding up, boy?
>> 海绵宝宝,
你还好吗，男孩？
>> Not so good,
Mr. Krabs.
>> 不太好，
蟹老板。
>> Hold on, now.
We're almost there.
>> 等等，现在。
我们快到了。
>> Two hours later...
>> 两个小时后...
>> Next!
>> 下一步！
>> We made it,
SpongeBob.
>> 我们做到了，
海绵宝宝。
We're in!
我们进来了！
>> Whoopee.
>> 哎呀。
>> All I know is,
chum is fum.
>> 我所知道的是，
密友很生气。
>> You said it.
Chum is fum.
>> 你说的是。
密友很生气。
>> Keep an eye peeled
for anything suspicierous.
>> Keep an eye peeled
对于任何可疑的事情。
>> Like that door?
>> 喜欢那扇门吗？
>> Mm, bingo!
>> Whoa.
>> 嗯，宾果游戏！
>> 哇哦。
>> Come on.
Giddyap, boy.
>> 来吧。
吉德亚普，男孩。
We're almost there.
我们快到了。
>> Excuse me.
>> 对不起。
Would you like
a free sample?
你愿意吗
免费样品？
>> No, uh...
>> 不，呃...
>> No?
How about your little friend?
>> 没有？
你的小朋友呢？
Hi, SpongeBob.
嗨，海绵宝宝。
>> Hi, I don't want
a free sample ei--
>> 嗨，我不想
免费样品 ei--
>> Sure, you do.
>> 当然，你知道。
Look out.
She's gonna blow!
当心。
她要爆炸了！
>>
>>
>> Well, Plankton obviously
didn't steal me formula.
>> 嗯，显然是浮游生物
没有偷我的配方。
So how did he steal
all me customers?
那么他是怎么偷的
都是我的顾客吗？
>> This chum tastes awful.
>> 这个朋友的味道很糟糕。
>> Yeah, but the slogan
is so catchy
>> 是的，但是口号
太吸引人了
that we can't stop eating it.
我们不能停止吃它。
>>
>>
Chum is fum!
密友很生气！
>> Come on, SpongeBob.
>> 来吧，海绵宝宝。
>> I'm gonna see how
our advertising guru is doing.
>> 我来看看如何
我们的广告大师正在做。
What brilliant slogans have you
come up with this week, Patrick?
你有什么精彩的口号
帕特里克，这周有什么安排吗？
>>
>>
Mm, huh?
>> Gah!
嗯，是吗？
>> 嘎！
You're supposed to be coming up
with witty catchphrases
你应该会来
并带有俏皮的口号
to keep
that rabble out there happy.
保留
外面的乌合之众很高兴。
Chum is fum.
密友很生气。
We've kind of got that one
already.
我们已经有了那个
已经。
>> Oh, I like that one!
>>哦，我喜欢那个！
>>
Oh, well.
>>
哦，好吧。
If it ain't broke,
don't fix it.
如果没坏的话
不要修复它。
Keep up the good work.
继续做好工作。
I guess.
我猜。
>> You got it, boss!
>> 老板，你明白了！
>> Hey, everyone.
>> 大家好。
Chum is fum!
密友很生气！
Hey, Karen,
check this out.
嘿，凯伦，
看看这个。
>> What now?
>> 现在怎么办？
>> You see,
every time I make a sale,
>> 你看，
每次我进行销售时，
the sound goes there.
声音传到那里。
Watch.
手表。
>>
>>
>> How is that gonna help
to boost sales?
>> 这有什么帮助
以促进销售？
>> Karen, babe,
you don't need help
>> 凯伦，宝贝，
你不需要帮助
when you got a catchy slogan
like mine.
当你有一个朗朗上口的口号时
就像我的一样。
>> Don't look now,
>> 现在别看，
but I think your catchy slogan's
days are numbered.
但我认为你的口号很吸引人
日子已经屈指可数了。
>>
Oh, something's not right.
>>
哦，有些不对劲。
>> Yeah, I know.
>> 是的，我知道。
I keep saying chum is fum,
but it's--
我一直说密友很fum，
但它是——
It's just not working.
它只是不起作用。
>> I'm out of here.
>> 我要离开这里了。
>> Hmm.
>> 嗯。
>>
>>
>> Patrick!
>> 帕特里克！
>> Huh?
What?
>> 嗯？
什么？
>> We're having a board meeting
here.
>> 我们正在召开董事会会议
在这里。
We need ideas.
我们需要想法。
>> Hmm.
>> 嗯。
Hmm.
Uh-huh.
唔。
嗯嗯。
I think I see the problem.
我想我看到了问题所在。
Your potty
has a shocky thing in it.
你的便盆
里面有令人震惊的事情。
>> No, that's not it,
you fool!
>> 不，不是这样的，
你这个傻瓜！
We need a new slogan.
我们需要一个新的口号。
You need to come up
with another genius catchphrase
你需要上来
还有另一个天才的口号
like chum is fum!
就像密友很生气一样！
But different.
但不同。
>> Oh, got ya.
>> 噢，明白了。
Hmm.
唔。
>> Three days later...
>> 三天后...
>> I'm so happy that they
changed that old, tired slogan,
>> 我很高兴他们
改变了那句老旧的口号，
Chum is fum.
密友很生气。
>> Yeah, that new slogan,
"fum is chum," is way cooler.
>> 是的，新口号，
“fum is chum”更酷。
>> Way cooler.
>> 凉爽多了。
>> Here's your
Chum Bucket Supreme.
>> 这是你的
密友桶至尊。
Enjoy!
享受！
Patrick, my boy,
帕特里克，我的孩子，
you really earned
that promotion.
你真的赚到了
那个促销。
>> Thanks, boss.
>> 谢谢老板。
>> Nothing can stop me now!
>> 现在没有什么可以阻止我了！
Ding!
叮！
>>
>>
♪ ♪
>> You fellows look hungry.
>> 你们这些家伙看起来很饿。
Here you go.
干得好。
>> Excuse me, sir.
>> 对不起，先生。
My resignation.
我的辞职。
>> But you're my whole
marketing department.
>> 但你是我的全部
营销部。
>> I know,
but I'm burned out.
>> 我知道，
但我已经筋疲力尽了。
See?
看？
Anyway, you can send my check
to my home.
不管怎样，你可以寄给我支票
到我家。
>> Check?
>> 检查？
You want money
for those stupid catchphrases?
你想要钱
为了那些愚蠢的口号？
Anybody can sell
to my idiot customers.
任何人都可以卖
给我的白痴顾客。
They're buffoons!
他们是小丑！
Morons!
白痴！
They'll buy anything
I sell them.
他们什么都会买
我卖掉它们。
They're the dumbest of the dumb.
他们是傻子中最傻的。
The stupidest of the stupid.
愚者中最愚者。
They're dummies, dweebs,
and doo-doo dunderheads.
他们是傻瓜，笨蛋，
和嘟嘟傻瓜。
I can keep that rabble
right where I want them.
我可以留住那群乌合之众
就在我想要它们的地方。
Huh?
啊？
>> What was that part
about doo-doo dunderheads, eh?
>> 那部分是什么
关于杜杜傻瓜，嗯？
>> Uh-oh.
>> 呃哦。
>> Where do you think
you're going, little man?
>> 你认为在哪里
你要去吗，小男人？
>> Is it too late
for sorry?
>> 是不是太晚了
抱歉？
Oh!
哦！
>>
>>
hey, check out that new sign
at the Krusty Krab.
嘿，看看那个新标志
在蟹堡王。
Who's hungry, Eh?
谁饿了，呃？
>> Well, Mr. K,
we're back in business.
>> 那么，K 先生，
我们恢复营业了。
>> Yep.
Keep up the good work, boyo!
>> 是的。
继续努力，男孩！
>> You got it, boss.
>> 老板，你明白了。
♪ ♪
>>
>>
>> Plankton, is that you?
>> 浮游生物，是你吗？
Welcome home, honey.
欢迎回家，亲爱的。
>>
>>
>> How was your day?
>> 你今天过得怎么样？
Dear Neptune, Plankton!
亲爱的海王星，浮游生物！
What is that smell?
那是什么气味？
>> The aroma you speak of,
Karen, my computer wife,
>> 你所说的香气，
凯伦，我的电脑妻子，
is the stench of failure.
是失败的恶臭。
>> Failure.
>> 失败。
>> And now the smell of defeat
so deeply penetrates my soul
>> 现在失败的味道
如此深深地渗透我的灵魂
that my very skin is permeated
with its foul stench.
我的皮肤都被渗透了
及其恶臭。
Thanks for asking.
谢谢你的询问。
>> Well, it smells horrible.
>> 呃，味道很难闻。
You're not coming in here
smelling like that.
你不会进来的
闻起来像那样。
>> Hey, what are you--
>> 嘿，你在做什么——
Stop that at once!
立刻停止吧！
You--
你 -
Oh, no!
哦，不！
>> There you go.
>> 就这样吧。
Now don't you feel better?
现在你不觉得好点了吗？
>> Although I do look ravishing,
>> 虽然我看起来很迷人，
it's not enough to mask
the ugliness I feel inside.
掩盖还不够
我内心感到的丑陋。
>> Did I miss a spot?
>> 我是不是漏掉了什么地方？
>>
>>
>> Don't blow a gasket, dear.
>> 亲爱的，不要吹掉垫圈。
Today's a special day.
今天是一个特别的日子。
>> Special day?
>> 特别的日子？
>> Yes, we're celebrating your
biggest accomplishment ever.
>> 是的，我们正在庆祝您
有史以来最大的成就。
>> Really?
I accomplished something?
>> 真的吗？
我完成了什么？
What is it?
它是什么？
>> It has something to do
with you
>> 有事可做
和你在一起
asking a certain someone
询问某人
to spend the rest of her life
with you.
度过余生
和你在一起。
>> What?
>> 什么？
>> We each wear rings
in memory of this moment.
>> 我们每个人都戴着戒指
纪念这一刻。
>> Enough with the riddles,
woman.
>> 谜语够了，
女人。
Just tell me what this
proud moment in my life is.
告诉我这是什么
我生命中值得骄傲的时刻是。
>> Oh, you selfish green twit.
>> 哦，你这个自私的绿色傻瓜。
It's our wedding anniversary.
这是我们的结婚纪念日。
>> Oh, that.
>> 哦，那个。
Yippee.
耶皮。
>>
>>
You forgot,
and I got you the perfect gift.
你忘了，
我给你准备了一份完美的礼物。
>> The Krabby Patty formula?
>> 蟹黄饼配方？
Mwah! Mwah!
哇！哇！
How did you get it?
你是怎么得到它的？
>> First
I went to the Krusty Krab.
>> 第一
我去了蟹堡王。
One Krabby Patty, please.
请来一份蟹肉饼。
Thank you.
谢谢。
>> Whatever.
>> 无论如何。
>> Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
>> 哇！哇！哇！
What?
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
什么？
抱歉，我没在听。
Well, you can tell me later.
嗯，你可以稍后告诉我。
>> You're not getting this
until you get me a gift.
>> 你没有明白这个
直到你给我送礼物。
>>
>>
>> From your heart.
>> 发自内心。
>>
>>
>> And that's the story
>> 这就是故事
of how I got my head
stuck in the fry vat.
我是如何得到我的头的
卡在炸缸里了。
>> That story gets better
every time you tell it, Sponge--
>> 这个故事变得更好了
每次你说出来的时候，海绵——
>> Hold on!
>> 坚持住！
Did you hear that?
你听到了吗？
It sounds like...
听起来像是...
>>
>>
>> Despair.
>> 绝望。
>> That was probably me.
>> 那可能就是我。
>> No, no, not bitterness.
Despair.
>> 不，不，不是苦涩。
绝望。
And it's coming from over...
而且是从那边传来的……
This way.
这边走。
Plankton.
浮游生物。
What's wrong, Plankton?
怎么了，浮游生物？
>> What?
SpongeBob?
>> 什么？
海绵宝宝？
Uh, there's nothing wrong.
呃，没有什么问题。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I'm fine.
我很好。
>> Come on,
tell your Uncle SpongeBob.
>> 来吧，
告诉你的海绵宝宝叔叔。
>> Oh, it's nothing.
>>哦，没什么。
It's just that today
is my wedding anniversary.
只是今天而已
是我的结婚纪念日。
>> Aw, what present
did you buy your wife, huh?
>> 噢，什么礼物
你老婆是你买的吧？
What did you buy her?
你给她买了什么？
>> Um, I didn't buy Karen
anything.
>> 嗯，我没有买凯伦
任何东西。
>>
>>
We've got a love emergency.
我们遇到了爱情紧急情况。
Attention, everyone.
大家注意了。
We have a love emergency.
我们遇到了爱情紧急情况。
Please stand back.
Love emergency.
请退后一点。
爱紧急情况。
Thank you.
Love emergency.
谢谢。
爱紧急情况。
Plankton,
there's only one thing to do.
浮游生物，
只有一件事要做。
You need to give her a present
from in here.
你需要给她一份礼物
从这里。
>> What,
like a kidney?
>> 什么，
像肾一样？
>> No, from the heart.
>> 不，是发自内心的。
That's where your love grows.
那就是你的爱成长的地方。
>> My what?
>> 我的什么？
>> Your love.
>> My loove?
>> 你的爱。
>> 我的爱人？
>> Love.
>> Loop?
>> 爱。
>> 循环？
>> Luh-vuh.
>> 呜呜。
>> Lump.
>> 肿块。
>> Say it with me:
>> 跟我一起说：
Uhl.
呃。
>> Uhl.
>> 呃。
>> Ahh.
>> 啊。
>> Vhh.
>> 唷。
>>
>>
>> Uh-luh-vuh.
>> 呃-呃-呃。
>> Love?
>> 爱？
>> That's it!
>> 就是这样！
You've taken the first step
into the halls of amm-nourv.
你已经迈出了第一步
进入amm-nourv的大厅。
Now, tell me more
about your Karen.
现在，告诉我更多
关于你的凯伦。
So what's your favorite thing
那么你最喜欢的事情是什么
for you and Karen
to do together?
为了你和凯伦
一起做？
>> Well, we like to take
long walks on the beach,
>> 好吧，我们喜欢采取
在海滩上长距离散步，
and we talk about our dreams--
我们谈论我们的梦想——
Uh, our dreams of conquering
all of Bikini Bottom
呃，我们的征服梦想
全部 比基尼泳裤
to become supreme overlords
of all creation
成为至高无上的霸主
一切造物的
and to trample our enemies
beneath our feet.
并践踏我们的敌人
在我们脚下。
Yeah!
是的！
>> Trampling enemies...
>> 践踏敌人...
Now, tell me about Karen.
现在，告诉我关于凯伦的事。
>> Well, she's a Mark II
Surplus UNIVAC
>> 嗯，她是 Mark II
剩余UNIVAC
with 256 gigs of RAM,
拥有 256 GB RAM，
and there's the cutest mole
on her CPU,
还有最可爱的鼹鼠
在她的CPU上，
and the way she processes data,
oh, ooh, mama.
以及她处理数据的方式，
哦，哦，妈妈。
>> Does she have any hobbies?
>> 她有什么爱好吗？
>> Uh, well, uh...
>> 呃，呃，呃……
She does make
a lot of beeping sounds.
她确实让
很多嘟嘟声。
>> Interesting.
Does she ever go "ding"?
>> 有趣。
她有“叮”过吗？
>> Now that you mention it,
she does go "ding,"
>> 既然你提到了，
她确实“叮”了一声
at least once a day.
每天至少一次。
>> Ohh, a music lover.
>> 哦，音乐爱好者。
I think we have our solution.
我想我们有我们的解决方案。
You need to serenade her.
你需要为她唱小夜曲。
>> Who, me?
I can't sing.
>> 谁，我？
我不会唱歌。
>> Not to worry.
>> 不用担心。
When you're done,
you'll be as...
当你完成后，
你会像...
♪ Golden-voiced
as me ♪
♪ 金嗓子
就像我一样♪
Repeat after me:
跟着我重复一遍：
♪ Me me me me me me mee ♪
♪ 我我我我我我我 ♪
>>
>>
♪ Me me me me mee ♪
Me--
♪ 我我我我我 ♪
我——
♪ Me meeee! ♪
♪ 我喵！ ♪
Whoo.
呼。
>> Oh, you are ready.
>> 哦，你准备好了。
>> Ready?
But what do I sing?
>> 准备好了吗？
但我唱什么呢？
>> Oh, when the time comes,
you'll know.
>> 哦，到时候，
你会知道的。
The music of love
comes from inside.
爱的音乐
来自内部。
>> Why are you so obsessed
with my internal organs?
>> 你为何如此着迷
用我的内脏？
>> This is it, Plankton.
>> 就是这样，浮游生物。
>> I don't think I'm ready.
>> 我认为我还没有准备好。
>> Oh, you just got butterflies
in your tummy.
>> 哦，你刚刚有了蝴蝶
在你的肚子里。
>> No, I'm just nervous.
>> 不，我只是紧张。
I don't know what flying insects
have to do with it.
不知道什么飞虫
与此有关。
>>
Get in there and sing,
>>
进去唱歌吧
you single-celled Romeo, you.
你这个单细胞罗密欧，你。
Ah, love-vuh.
啊，爱-呜。
>>
>>
Karen?
凯伦？
>> Plankton.
>> 浮游生物。
I don't see any present.
我没有看到任何礼物。
>> Oh, I have it.
>>哦，我有。
It's right here
in my kidney--I mean heart!
就在这里
在我的肾脏里——我是说心脏！
♪ Me me me me ♪
♪ 我我我我 ♪
♪ Me me ♪
♪ 我我 ♪
♪ Oh, my Karen,
oh, my Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的凯伦，
哦，我的凯伦♪
♪ Oh, my computer wife,
Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的电脑妻子，
凯伦♪
♪ Put down those punch cards ♪
♪ 放下那些打孔卡 ♪
♪ And listen to my ode ♪
♪ 听我的颂歌 ♪
♪ Oh, my Karen,
oh, my Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的凯伦，
哦，我的凯伦♪
♪ Oh, my computer wife,
Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的电脑妻子，
凯伦♪
♪ What compares to ♪
♪ 与什么相比 ♪
Uh...
呃...
Aha!
啊哈！
♪ Your beautiful diodes ♪
♪ 你美丽的二极管 ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, my Karen,
oh, my Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的凯伦，
哦，我的凯伦♪
♪ Oh, my computer wife,
Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的电脑妻子，
凯伦♪
♪ I was blinded ♪
♪ 我被蒙蔽了 ♪
♪ Yes, I was blinded ♪
♪ 是的，我被蒙蔽了 ♪
♪ I was blinded by the light
of your cathode ray ♪
♪ 我被灯光弄瞎了
你的阴极射线 ♪
♪ Oh, I built you ♪
♪ 哦，我创造了你 ♪
♪ Yes, I built you ♪
♪ 是的，我创造了你 ♪
♪ I built you in the... ♪
Uh...
♪ 我把你建造在... ♪
呃...
Um, hmm.
嗯，嗯。
♪ In the shape of a cube ♪
♪ 立方体形状 ♪
♪ Oh, my Karen,
oh, my Karen ♪
♪ 哦，我的凯伦，
哦，我的凯伦♪
♪ You'll never know how much
I love your vacuum tubes ♪
♪ 你永远不会知道有多少
我喜欢你的真空管 ♪
♪ ♪
>>
>>
That was so beautiful.
那真是太美了。
>> You really liked it?
>> 你真的喜欢它吗？
>> I loved it!
>> 我喜欢它！
But not as much
as I love you, Plankton.
但没有那么多
正如我爱你，浮游生物。
>> I luh..uh...
>> 我呃..呃...
Love you too.
我也爱你。
All: Aw.
全体：噢。
>> So can I have my present now?
>> 那么我现在可以收到礼物了吗？
>> Of course,
my little overlord.
>> 当然，
我的小霸主
Now loading
the Krabby Patty formula.
正在加载
蟹黄饼配方。
>> They're such a lovely couple.
>> 他们真是一对可爱的情侣。
>> Yes,
you porous kitchen utensil!
>> 是的，
你这个多孔的厨房用具！
By helping me woo
my computer wife,
通过帮助我求爱
我的电脑老婆
you've just doomed
the Krusty Krab.
你已经注定了
蟹堡王。
>> Oh, no!
>> 哦，不！
I've got to stop it
before it's too late.
我必须阻止它
以免为时已晚。
>> 45% loaded.
>> 已加载 45%。
>> Control, alt, delete.
>> 控制、替代、删除。
>> 55% loaded.
>> 已加载 55%。
>> How do you
turn this thing off?
>> 你怎么样
把这个东西关掉？
>> Get your hands
off my wife!
>> 伸出你的手
放开我的妻子！
>> 65% loaded.
>> 已加载 65%。
>> The plug.
>> 插头。
>>
>>
>> Aha!
>> 啊哈！
You lose, Plankton.
你输了，浮游生物。
>> Oh, no!
>> 哦，不！
You unplugged the coffeemaker,
SpongeBob.
你拔掉咖啡机的插头
海绵宝宝。
>>
I am so fired.
>>
我被解雇了。
>> Loading Krabby Patty formula.
>> 加载蟹黄饼配方。
>> Here it comes!
>> 它来了！
>> Oh, Plankton,
you've made me so happy.
>> 哦，浮游生物，
你让我很开心。
>> That's fantastic.
>> 太棒了。
Where's that formula?
那个公式在哪里？
>> I'm crying.
>> 我哭了。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
>> Karen, what's wrong?
>> 凯伦，怎么了？
Have you sprung a leak?
你有漏水吗？
>> No, I'm just so happy.
>> 不，我只是太高兴了。
I--I'm crying
with tears of joy.
我——我哭了
带着喜悦的泪水。
>> But you're shorting out.
>> 但你已经短路了。
>> I'm just--
>> 我只是——
Krabby Patty formula
loading completed.
蟹黄饼配方
加载完成。
>> Yes!
>> 是的！
>> No!
>> 不！
Boom!
繁荣！
>> No!
>> 不！
>> Yes!
I'm saved!
>> 是的！
我得救了！
Your wife exploded!
你老婆爆炸了！
Um, happy anniversary,
you guys.
嗯，周年纪念快乐，
你们。
>> Rebooting.
>> 重新启动。
>> Loading EMILP.
>> 加载 EMILP。
>> EMILP?
>> EMILP？
What's EMILP?
什么是 EMILP？
>> Emergency
Mother-In-Law Program.
>> 紧急情况
婆婆计划。
>> Oh, no.
>> 哦，不。
>> Plankton, what have you done
to my daughter?
>> 浮游生物，你做了什么
给我女儿？
You made her cry.
你让她哭了。
You know, she could have been
with an ATM,
你知道，她本来可以
有自动取款机，
someone with money,
but she chose you.
有钱的人，
但她选择了你。
I don't know why.
我不知道为什么。
♪ ♪